Th-This can't be happening!
Even Groribas, our best warrior was defeated?!
Just what kind of creature is he ?
How he got on the ship anyway?{What manner of creature is he?
And how'd he get aboard?}
Damn it!
Melzargard was supposed
to be guarding the ship!
Now he and I are
the only elite fighters left!
I bet he's just mucking about...
I need him now!
Curse the bastard!
Geryuganshoop,
what is the problem?
Lord Boros!
I-I'm terribly sorry.
I've allowed one of the natives
to infiltrate the ship.
In the mere four minutes
since coming aboard,
he has damaged 23%
of the ship.
It seems he is alone,
but he has managed
to instantly kill
every warrior sent to
intercept him.
Do not panic.
As long as the power sphere
is safe,
the ship will not go down.
The damage so far is limited to
the crew's living quarters.
But minnows won't be enough.
Geryuganshoop...
you, Groribas and Melzargard,
my top lieutenants,
will go eliminate this intruder.
Groribas has fallen, sir...
What?
Let me get Melzargard back here!
He and I together will wipe out
the intruder without fail!
THE DOMINATOR OF THE UNIVERSE
Shoutout to YouTubers :
[ Raito ], AnnieMay MissHurt  &   Isaiah Leblanc
One ponch!!!
Three, two, one, kiss Joe
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
Sir Joe, Kiss Joe, Shit Joe, Side Joe!
nan datten da, frustration
Massive glitter, Restoration?  ☻
ore wa tomaranai
What about tomorrow night?!!
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One ponch, can you make shit and let it show?
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
All of the cocks, too many cocks, Soooooo?
power, get power
Power, ghetto power
girigiri genkai made
Kitty Kitty, can you tie my DICK?
Key whore
ore o tataeru koe ya
Poor little duck, the heir of Korea
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
Cat's eye?, Nah. Take a shit through the night
He row!
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
The car, oh, take a shit in zoo,
the cool toe of the macau.
Never take a nap, Oh yeah!
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Soda, don't worry; Oh she oh sang with a Key!
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
Ole wah, still don't care, what? she high!
Kill rock!
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
The lava, to kill a key capture you shit, out away.
tatakau hero
The tech guy oh!  Key row
kodoku na hero
Color Cora Key Whore
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be a Psycho Hero!
m 0 0 l 1105 0 1105 88 0 88
MYSTERY CRAFT IN SKIES ABOVE CITY A
We have more information on
the enormous flying object
that suddenly appeared
in the skies over City A.
I'm here at the scene.
As you can see, all the main roads
leading to City A have been closed,
and officials are on high alert.
According to survivors,
City A has been almost
entirely demolished.
EMPLOYMENT APPLICATION
NAME: HAMMERHEAD
m 0 0 l 1105 0 1105 88 0 88
MYSTERY CRAFT IN SKIES ABOVE CITY A
This image of the giant flying object
was captured with a telephoto lens.
What are your thoughts?
Most likely, this is the act of
an alien or extraterrestrial being.
Or perhaps it's an
unidentified life-form
that has a highly advanced
civilization unbeknownst to us.
Of course, other possibilities exist as well.
I see.
Also, there have been
eyewitness accounts of
very powerful life-forms
descending to the ground
from the spacecraft.
Several Class S heroes are presently
at the location tackling the issue.
He pummeled that thing with
nothing but his bare fists.
That's a Class S for you.
But even so...
It's still no good!
It possesses incredible regenerative powers.
And don't let it hit any part of you.
A single blow instantly tore my arm off.
Dodge its attacks at all costs!
If I may cut in...
Shall we use a bombardment
to finish them off?
That is good.
Contact the ship.
I will go.
Get back here!
You scum!
Don't you underestimate me, bastart!
I hope you like mincemeat, freak!
Melzargard! What are you doing?!
I'm in battle.
We have an intruder!
Ridiculous.
It's true. Finish them off
and get up here quickly!
This one's locked too...
Hey, open up! You've got a visitor!
Oops... I broke it.
I've decided.
I'm going to rip your limbs off,
then keep you as the ship mascot.
That is good.
Pulled yourself together again, eh?
I'm gonna keep you
for batting practice!
Everyone! It seems that direct physical attacks{Comrades! It may be that
direct physical attacks}
have no effect on him!
Let's withdraw for now...
and think of a way to destroy it,
like heat or something!
Smashing is all I can do! Forget it!
This is all I know, too.
Can't teach an old dog new tricks.
Me, too. Sorry, sweet Iairon!
Iai, don't you have faith in me?
There's nothing I can't cut down.
It's pointless...
These guys aren't the type to listen.
Melzargard!
Look, I really need you on the ship.
Getting rid of the intruder takes priority.
I'd love to, but I'm busy.
These creatures are persistent.
What the hell?
The life forms down there
are proving tough to handle too?
Nothing tough about them.
What's with the ship?
Is it going down?
It's not going down,
but more than half
the crew have been killed.
What the hell?!
Listen. Begin cleansing my location
with a bombardment from the ship!
I've got my hands full right now.
Besides, artillery bombardment is
the job of the lower ranks.
Well, I'm in a situation where
I can't return to the ship.
All right.
I'll notify the artillery crews.
Don't get caught up in
the barrage and die.
Hey, wait!
You should come down here
and help me.
That'd be much faster.
Oi! Geryuganshoop!
Damn him. How tough is this intruder?
How about another one?!
More futile attacks.
Although you are exhausting
yourself. That is good.
The hell is this?
A marble? Why've you got this?
Give it back!
Sure thing.
Damn!
That's nasty, you nasty bastard!
You dead?
Hey, this guy's got marble-
looking things inside him.
That's where you hurt him!
Oh!
Nice work.
So I just have to keep slicing
until I hit a vital marble!
Impossible!
I've been growing that head
for a hundred years!
It died in a dump like this?
But you scum are all dead
when the shells hit.
They're on their way!
Attention, intruder!
Stop your destructive acts
and leave this instant.
Attention, intruder!
Leave immediately.
Otherwise, we will unleash
all our forces against you!
What's that?
I hear a voice right inside my head.
Take one more step...
...and you're dead!
Even if I wanted to get out,
I can't. I've lost my way!
Really? You'll leave?
All right, I will guide you.
Take a right, then go
up the stairs there.
A right?
Exactly, a right.
I guess I'll go left!
No, wait! Not that way!
W-W-Wait...
Hang on! You can't...!
All right, that was my fault!
I'll come to you.
Please stay right there.
Ahhh! Noooo!
Now this place looks like
a control room or something.
You...
An octopus?
You dare go around
busting up our ship?
Hey! The debris is all flying at me!
Now Geryuganshoop, the supreme
telekinetic power in the universe,
will grind you into blood sausage.
Editor & Timer :
ScavvyKiD
[AnimeRG]
Sub General: IsoTropic
Sub Soldier: KoTuWa
Editor & Timer :
ScavvyKiD
[AnimeRG]
Sub General: IsoTropic
Sub Soldier: KoTuWa
Editor & Timer :
ScavvyKiD
[AnimeRG]
Sub General: IsoTropic
Sub Soldier: KoTuWa
Editor & Timer :
ScavvyKiD
[AnimeRG]
Sub General: IsoTropic
Sub Soldier: KoTuWa
Just about there.
Lord Geryuganshoop,
preparations for the bombardment
are nearly complete.
Shall I proceed?
Maybe he went to the bathroom...
Hey, Lord Geryuganshoop!
Telekinetic power...like a psychic?
You leave me no choice.
Super Telekinetic Gravitational Wave!
Die, Earthling!
My unparalleled telekinetic powers allow me
to manipulate even the forces of gravity!
Have you any idea
what a black hole is, you ape?
Inside one, the gravitational
effects are so strong
even light itself cannot escape!
Wait...?
Now what is he doing?
Take this!
Telekinetic Shower of Rubble!
I got him!
What a waste of psychic powers.
I mean, all you're doing
is tossing pebbles around.
Anyone can do that.
How...could...
I...Geryuganshoop...
be...
Excuse me—
Can I ask...
...where your boss is?
This looks bad.
Is that confirmed?
Yes, Child Emperor said that
the energy level in
the spaceship is rapidly rising.
Yes, but the civilians—
Recall the search and
rescue teams for now.
Have everyone take cover.
You'll be taking fire soon!
Hop on!
There we go.
Geryuganshoop still hasn't
gotten back to me...
but whatever.
Let's see...
I believe the order was
to concentrate fire
around the enemies on
the surface near Melzargard.
Now only two more heads to go!
I'll bust 'em wide open!
Is it time?
Ship, bombardment, coming...
There they are.
All right...
click!
It's over.
Evasion, impossible.
Instant death.
Huh... What happened?
What on earth?
They stopped.
All of you would be dead without me.
Can't you even finish one small fry?
Maybe try starting over from Class C.
You can have...
your shells back.
Th-This is...
I wanna go home.
I didn't expect you to be here.
Thank you, Mumen Rider.
Which areas are likely
to have survivors?
There must be more out there.
But you...
I'll go rescue them right now.
We want to know, too.
Yeah, can't let him hog the limelight.
Stinger, Lightning Max...
Mind if we borrow this?
You guys...
Nice catch.
Found it...
Smush.
One left!
Silverfang!
A...direct hit.
Weak, weak!
You are all so very weak.
Dead after a single hit!
A change of tactics was all I needed.
If I forget defense and focus on attack,
this will all be over quickly.
And you're next!
I will spring past that sword and
squeeze your skull 'til it pops.
If you think so? Then be my guest.
So he's here.
This planet's finest warrior...
I can sense no limit to his energy.
You the boss of these invaders?
Wonderful!
Before we fight, let us exchange names.
I lead the pirate band known as Dark Matter,
and dominator of the universe,{.
I am} Boros.
I'm a hero for fu—I mean,
a professional hero.
My name's Saitama.
Saitama...
Look, I don't know what
the Denominator of the Universe
wants with Earth...
...but you sure trashed City A.
What I want with Earth?
There exists a prophecy.
Prophecy? You mean...
Once, I traveled the universe,
ravaging everything in sight.
But I was too strong.
Eventually, there were none left
who could face me.
I came to know the torment of utter,
all-encompassing boredom.
Then one day, a seer told me...
On a faraway planet,
a being exists who is my match,
one who could rekindle
my passion for battle.
That was nearly twenty years ago.
Do you have any idea about the
distance I had to travel to get here?{Have you any idea the distance
I have traveled to get here?}
My men thought the prophecy
was a ruse,
made up to lure me away...
But now I am certain.
Come. Give stimulation
to my existence.
That is why I am here!
Are you stupid?
You can't just go around
attacking other planets
just to liven up your boring life.
Even telemarketers wouldn't think that.
This set of armor, used to seal
my immeasurable, irresistible power...
...has now been broken.
OK.
Here I come!
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
NEXT
TIME
THE STRONGEST HERO
The next... and final episode of One-Punch Man is...
"The Strongest Hero."
What does it mean to be "Strongest", Saitama?
You must tell me too...